[Music]
Hey guys, you and I both have been
waiting for this video for far too long.
Today is Thursday, August 28th. My
flight back to Brown is on August 31st,
which is this upcoming Sunday. I have
not started packing at all. I actually
just finished editing one of my New York
vlogs, but the packing must commence.
For context, I'm a rising junior at
Brown University. I live in Southern
California, so it is quite the trek to
get to Providence, Rhode Island every
single time. But because I am a rising
junior, I have a lot of things stored in
Providence. And because I've done two
rounds of moving in and moving out, I'd
like to think I got a lot better at it.
Freshman year, my parents both came with
me. Sophomore year, my mom came with me.
And then this year, my brother's
actually coming with me. I'm still
drumming this here because I've
>> Can you be quiet? I'm vlogging.
>> Hey, vlog. If yall don't know, Irene's
room is actually so dirty. It's never
messy.
>> It's not how she She's not how she
presents herself.
>> Anyways, I think I have gotten better at
packing. So, I've been pushing it off
longer than I usually do. But, I have a
pretty packed schedule on Friday,
Saturday, Sunday, which means I kind of
only have tonight and then like tomorrow
morning afternoon to pack my whole life
together. I'm going abroad in the
spring, which means I'm going to have to
move out at the end of this semester, so
I don't need to pack too much. Yeah, the
beginning of this vlog will just be me
packing everything and then we will fly
out back to campus. Hey guys, it's the
next day. It's Friday, so I actually
didn't end up packing anything
yesterday. So, I basically only have
today to finish everything up. I do go
on a little shopping spree with the
excuse of going back to school. So, I
have a small haul. Okay, we're going to
go through this quick. Okay, so from
Paxon Brandy, the first thing I got is
the tank that I wore yesterday. I also
got these shorts, but I mainly got these
as PJs from Garage. I got another cami
tank. This is a navy. I adore these. I
want to grow a little collection of
these just because I do reach for them
super often. I also got this top from
Garage and it ties in the back and it's
like open back. I kind of avoid denim
skirts, but this one was actually pretty
comfortable and I loved the pocket
detailing. And then lastly from
Hollister, I just got this white
sweater. It's cable knit. I thought the
little Hollister logo was very early
2000's core. I feel like Abberrombie
also did this and I kind of love it. And
then also the glasses that I wore
yesterday, these are from Idea Optics,
but I worked with them on TikTok and
Instagram, but these are my new blue
light glasses because I lost the ones
I've been using in Brooklyn when I was
back in New York. So, I was glad that
they reached out. All right, that's the
haul. Let's get packing now.
the one in my cr.
[Music]
>> All right. I have to fold all this and
then I'm going to try to put them in
vacuum seal bags.
[Music]
If you guys travel a lot or if you're a
college student who has to just move
back and forth all the time, I'm telling
you, vacuum sealed bags have saved my
life. Yes, your suitcase ends up really
heavy, but that's the only way you'll
fit your life into a couple suitcases.
But yeah, if you're not on that already,
you got to get on it.
foreign.
[Music]
Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
The poor dam
Oh, you Bye.
>> We are at the airport, but we're too
early that we can't even check in our
bags yet. But this is my brother's first
time coming with me to Brown.
>> 6:30, flight at 9. Nowhere to check our
bags.
>> What's going on?
[Music]
>> Drew my heart,
but I felt things were better now. I
belong in your arms. Got a paper cup
full of wine, a play of Charles Bridge
on a side.
>> I abandoned my brother and went to TSA
Pre, but now I'm just waiting for him.
He's picking up the suitcase and we
shall take the shuttle to the gate,
which is always annoying, but we're
super early anyway, so doesn't really
matter. Security done.
Hope I'm not so out of line. Your point
of view different
>> guys. What the heck? Wait, this is so
cute. How much is this, John?
>> 32.
>> 32 bucks.
>> Who is 32 for this?
>> We made it to our gate with an hour to
spare. I'm going to do some editing.
Tell them what you're going to do.
>> He's going to rot on his phone.
>> That's what I learned. and we will catch
you on the flight.
We're boarding.
We have boarded. Is there anything you
want to say?
5 hours and 45 minutes and then we land
at 6:00 a.m. in Providence, Rhode
Island.
>> I ended up behind Irene. I don't know
how this happened.
>> How do you feel about starting junior
year?
>> Let's not think about it.
>> We just We're just going to do it.
[Music]
Yeah. No.
>> Hey guys, real quick, I'd like to thank
Mini Me for sponsoring today's video.
You guys can watch me decorate my new
room while I talk about Mini Me. During
my time in college, I've really noticed
the importance of self-reflection,
particularly through journaling. There's
always so much going on externally and
internally, and having a space that
keeps you grounded is so helpful. Mini
Me is a journaling and mood tracking app
that supports emotional well-being by
giving you a safe and private space to
reflect. It remembers your past entries,
creates prompts that actually connect
with what you've written before, and
provides weekly summaries that turn all
of your reflections into a bigger story.
Mini aims to make journaling feel
natural and personal so you can better
understand your emotions organically.
I'll drop Mini Mi's link in the
description if you want to check it out.
Thank you again to Mini Me for
sponsoring today's video. And let's get
back to it.
Bag secured. Now we need to go find
Lorena. Yeah,
>> we're back at Brown University. Going to
get my keys real quick and then moving
me in. But Lorena's over there with her
car. Ti Lorena. I haven't walked this
treacherous staircase in so long. Good
morning. Can I pick up my keys? Thank
you.
[Music]
up
in your love
[Music]
And I got me going crazy. Someone just
tell me why I do
So
this is
>> she's helping me.
[Music]
>> Okay, we're finding shampoo for me. I
usually get this one, but they don't
have the matching shampoo, and I don't
really like that.
>> Sad.
>> So, maybe we'll get this and this.
That's what you do, right?
>> Mhm. Beautiful.
[Music]
>> Not.
>> Hey guys, this is the room. It's much
smaller than last year. I think she's
still cute. The walls are much cleaner,
but we're going to start figuring out
furniture and wedding stuff away.
[Music]
Look at me baby
lonely
baby just like a drink.
[Music]
You make me go crazy. All the little
things you do. You're my teddy bear.
Teddy bear.
You learn about the tr
[Music]
[Applause]